Guide to the Institute of Pacific Relations Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Part II. American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-1959 and Miscellaneous Committee Files
  - American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-1959 and Miscellaneous Committee Files
    - General Correspondence, 1953-1954
      - Herald Tribune--Article, 1954 January 8 (Box 279)
      - Hersey, John (Box 279)
      - Holland, William L. (Box 279)
      - Johnson, Joseph E. (Box 279)
      - Kizer, Benjamin H. (Box 279)
      - Lilienthal, David E. (Box 279)
      - Little, Herbert S. (Box 279)
      - Malott, Deane W. (Box 279)
      - Martin, Charles E. (Box 279)
      - Mayer, Albert (Box 279)
      - Memorandum approved by AIPR Planning Committee on Possibilities of Support for a Proposed New Council on Asian Affairs, 1954 October 19 (Box 279)
      - Murphy, J. Morden--Letters concerning Planning Committee (Box 279)
      - Press Release, 1953 December 11 (Box 279)
      - Reischauer, Edwin O. (Box 279)
      - Some Points for Consideration by the Planning Committee, 1954 June 24 (Box 279)
      - Swope, Gerard (Box 279)
      - Trustees Replies, 1953 November (Box 279)
      - Waymack, W.W. (Box 279)
    - General Correspondence, 1955-1959
      - Annual Meeting of Members (with ballots) (Box 280)
        - 1956 June (Box 280)
        - 1957 June (Box 280)
        - 1958 June (Box 280)
        - 1959 June (Box 280)
      - Asia Society Release, 1956 December 4 (Box 280)
      - Biggerstaff, Knight (Box 280)
      - Board of Trustees
        - 1955-1956 (Box 280)
        - 1956 June (Box 280)
        - Annual Meeting
          - 1956 June 21 (Box 280)
          - 1957 June (Box 280)
      - Distribution of Documents to Trustees, 1955 (Box 280)
      - Emerson, Rupert and John K. Fairbank (Box 280)
      - Executive Committee
        - 1955 January 13 (Box 280)
        - Agenda, 1955 November 29 (Box 280)
        - Minutes
          - 1955 April 28 (Box 280)
          - 1955 September 13 (Box 280)
          - 1955 November 29 (Box 280)
          - 1956 February 21 (Box 280)
          - 1958 January 13 (Box 280)
          - 1958 April 24 (Box 280)
      - Goodrich, L. Carrington (Box 280)
      - Holland, William L. (Box 280)
      - Immediate Release, 1955 October 13 (Box 280)
      - Kades, Chas L. (Box 280)
      - Members and Friends of AIPR (Box 280)
      - Mitrany, David (Box 280)
      - Murphy, J. Morden (Box 280)
      - The Nation--Editoral Comment, 1955 November 5 (Box 280)
      - New York Herald Tribune, 1955 October 13 (Box 280)
      - New York Times--Editorial, 1957 December 3 (Box 280)
      - Sacramento Bee--Editorial Comment, 1955 November 22 (Box 280)
      - Statement by Pacific Institute on Loss of Tax Exemption, 1955 October 18 (Box 280)
      - Statement of Receipts and Expenditures
        - 1954 January-1955 January 31 (Box 280)
        - 1955 January 1-December 1 (Box 280)
        - 1956 January 1-December 1 (Box 280)
        - 1957 January 1-December 31 (Box 280)
      - Supplementary Notes on Later Responses on Prospect for a New Asian Organization, 1955 May 5 (Box 280)
      - The Washington Post--Editorial Comment, 1955 November 5 (Box 280)
      - Wright, Quincy (Box 280)
    - Planning Committee, 1954
      - Agendas (Box 281)
      - By-laws of AIPR, 1946 November 26 (Box 281)
      - Certificate of Incorporation Amended, 1946 November (Box 281)
      - General Correspondence
        - Fairbank, John K., 1954 April 22 (Box 281)
        - Holland, William to Members of AIPR, 1954 April 22 (Box 281)
        - Holland, William replies to J. Morden Murphy, 1954 July-December (Box 281)
        - Martin, C.E. from Tokyo, 1954 October 15 (Box 281)
        - Murphy, J. Morden, 1954 July-December (Folders 1 & 2) (Box 281)
        - Rockwood, C.P., 1954 July-December (Box 281)
      - Memo:
        - Borton, Hugh--Planning Committee Report, 1954 October 4 (Box 281)
        - Cleveland, Harlan--Planning Committee Report, 1954 October 5 (Box 281)
        - Fisher, Harold to Gerald Swope with attached letter. (Box 281)
        - Holland, William to Hugh Borton & J. Morden Murphy, 1954 May 6 (Box 281)
        - Holland, William to J. Morden Murphy, 1954 December 4 (Box 281)
        - Mayer, Albert to Planning Committee, 1954 September 29 (Box 281)
        - Mayer, Albert to Planning Committee, 1954 October 6 (Box 281)
        - Murphy, J. Morden-- Memo approved by AIPR Planning Committee setting forth agreed basis on which a number of its members shall approach designated outside persons to determine the possibilities of support for a proposed new Council on Asian Affairs. (Box 281)
      - Minutes
        - 1954 July 22 (Box 282)
        - 1954 September 8 (Box 282)
        - 1954 September 22 (Box 282)
        - 1954 October 19 (Box 282)
      - Name Lists (Box 282)
      - Notes on recent of groups interested in forming organization concerned with Asian Affairs with supplementary notes (Box 282)
      - Questions on the need for an American Agency on Asian Affairs (Folders 1 & 2) (Box 282)
      - Reports and Recommendations of Planning Committee, 1954 December 20 (Box 282)
      - Sub-Committee Report to Planning Committee including three memos from Borton, Mayer and Cleveland, 1954 October 11 (Box 282)
    - International Research Committee
      - Allen & Unwin Ltd., 1936-1934 (Box 283)
      - Alsberg, Carl L.
        - 1937 (Box 283)
        - Land Utilization (Box 283)
      - American Committee for International Studies, 1940 (Box 283)
      - American Council
        - 1945-1946 (Box 283)
        - Hawaii, 1932-1934, 1946 (Box 283)
        - Los Angeles, 1946 (Box 283)
        - New York, 1936-1937, 1945-1946 (Box 283)
        - San Francisco, 1945-1946 (Box 283)
        - Washington, D.C., 1945-1946 (Box 283)
      - Austern, Hilda, 1936-1937, 1944 (Box 283)
      - Australian Institute of International Affairs, 1933-1934, 1936-1937, 1945-1946 (Box 283)
      - Belshaw, Horace
        - 1936-1934 (Box 284)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 284)
        - Economic Organization (Box 284)
        - Land Tenure and the Problem of Tenurial Reform in New Zealand (Box 284)
        - Miscellaneous Manuscripts (Box 284)
        - New Zealand, 1944-1947 (Box 284)
        - New Zealand in the Post-War World, 1945 (Box 284)
      - Broek, Jan O.M.--Economic Geography of Southeast Asia, 1943-1949 (Box 284)
      - Buck, John Lossing, 1934-1935, 1936-1937 (Box 284)
      - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1933, 1936-1937, 1945-1946 (Box 285)
      - Carter, Edward C., 1937-1941, 1943, 1945 (Box 285)
      - Chandrasekhar, S.--India’s Hungry Millions, 1944-1946 (Box 285)
      - Chin, Rockwood Q.P., 1944-1946 (Box 285)
      - China Institute of Pacific Relations, 1933-1934, 1945-1946 (Box 285)
      - Cleeve, Margaret, 1936-1937 (Box 285)
      - Columbia University Press, 1936 (Box 285)
      - Comité d'Études des Problemes du Pacifique, 1945-1946 (Box 285)
      - Condliffe, J.B.--International Collaboration in the Study of International Relations, 1930 (Box 285)
      - Conference
        - Shanghai, 1931 October (Box 286)
        - Banff, 1933 August (Box 286)
        - Tokyo, 1935 April (Box 286)
        - [Yosemite?], 1936 August (Box 286)
        - Hot Springs, 1945 January (Box 286)
        - Atlantic City, 1946 January (Box 286)
      - Corbett, Percy E., 1945 (Box 286)
      - Cultural Relations (Box 286)
      - Dennet, Tyler--Security in the Pacific and the Far East, 1942 (Box 286)
      - Discussion Meetings (Box 286)
      - Fang, Fu-an--Economic Shanghai During the Pacific War 1941-1945, 1946 (Box 286)
      - Far Eastern Who's Who, 1949 (Box 286)
      - Farley, Miriam S.--American Far Eastern Policy Since V-J Day, 1948-1949 (Box 286)
      - Feuer, Lewis, 1945-1946 (Box 286)
      - Field, Frederick V.
        - 1937-1939 (Box 286)
        - The Situation in the Pacific Area, 1932 (Box 286)
      - Finances
        - 1930-1934 (Box 286)
        - 1936, 1945 (Box 286)
        - Pacific Council, 1945 (Box 286)
      - Fisher, Galen M., 1935, 1937 (Box 286)
      - Fisher, Joseph L., 1948-1949 (Box 286)
      - Friedman, Irving S.--Financial Reconstruction in the Far East, 1946-1950 (Box 287)
      - Garnett, A. Campbell, 1945 (Box 287)
      - Greene, Jerome D., 1939 (Box 287)
      - Harvard Radcliffe Bureau of International Research, 1937 (Box 287)
      - Heyworth, Roger H.--The Vegetable Oil and Oilseed Trade as a Factor in...China, 1944 (Box 287)
      - Ho, Franklin, 1933-1935 (Box 287)
      - Holland, William L.
        - 1935-1938 (Box 287)
        - 1944-1945 (Box 287)
        - 1946 (Box 287)
        - Commodity Control in the Pacific, 1936 (Box 287)
        - Office Expenses (Box 287)
        - Population Problems and Policies in the Far East (Box 287)
      - Hopkins, Garland E., 1950 (Box 287)
      - Hsü, Y.Y., 1945-1946 (Box 287)
      - Hubbard, G.E., 1936-1937 (Box 287)
      - Huntington, Emily--Living on a Moderate Income, 1937 (Box 287)
      - Indian Council of World Affairs, 1945-1946 (Box 288)
      - Indian Institute of International Affairs, 1945-1946 (Box 288)
      - International Labor Office, 1934-1936 (Box 288)
      - Ito, Choji, 1935-1936 (Box 288)
      - Japanese Council
        - 1931-1935 (Box 288)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 288)
        - Office Expenses (Box 288)
      - Jenkins, David, 1948-1950 (Box 288)
      - Jenkins, Shirley--American Economic Policy Toward the Philippines, 1947-1951 (Box 288)
      - Kelly & Walsh Ltd., 1934, 1936-1937 (Box 288)
      - Kollewijn, R.D.-- A Suggestion for the Undertaking of Research Work in the Field of Private Law (Box 288)
      - Kuczynski, Robert, 1943-1945 (Box 288)
      - Lang, Olga--Chinese Family and Society, 1944-1946 (Box 289)
      - Lasker, Bruno, 1949-1950 (Box 289)
      - Lawrence, Leonard L., 1945 (Box 289)
      - League of Nations, 1936-1937 (Box 289)
      - Lieu, D.K., 1933-1934, 1944-1945 (Box 289)
      - Lilienthal, Philip E., 1946 (Box 289)
      - Lind, Andrew W.--Hawaii in the Making, 1946-1949 (Box 289)
      - Liu, Yu-wan (Wellington), 1933-1934, 1936-1937 (Box 289)
      - Lockwood, William W., 1937-1938, 1940 (Box 289)
      - Lorwin, Lewis L., 1933 (Box 289)
      - Marvin, Langdon P., Jr. and Hardenbergh, Mary N.--Air Import Potentials: China to USA, 1947-1948 (Box 289)
      - Mason, Leonard, 1948-1949 (Box 289)
      - Maynard, L.A.--The Improvement of the Diet of the Chinese Farm Family (Box 289)
      - Michael, Franz H. - 191^5-191+7 (Box 289)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 289)
      - Moore, Harriet, 1944-1946 (see also Pratt, Helen) (Box 289)
      - Nasu, Shiroshi, 1933 (Box 289)
      - Netherlands and Netherlands Indies Council, 1936-1937, 1945-1946 (Box 289)
      - New Zealand Institute of International Affairs, 1935-1937, 1945-1946 (Box 289)
      - Nishikiori, Hideo, 1945 (Box 289)
      - Oxford University Press (Box 289)
      - Pacific Affairs, 1945 (Box 289)
      - Pacific Shipping Project (Box 289)
      - Philippine Council
        - 1936-1937, 1945-1946 (Box 290)
        - Public Opinion Project (Box 290)
      - Pratt, Helen G. and Moore, Harriet--Russia: A Short History, 1945-1948 (see also Moore, Harriet) (Box 290)
      - Research
        - Discontinued Projects (Box 290)
        - Personnel, 1945 (Box 290)
        - Policy, 1929-1933 (Box 290)
        - Program, 1928-1935 (Box 290)
        - Proposals, 1932-1933, 1946-1948 (2 Folders) (Box 290)
        - Reports, 1929-1936, 1945 (Box 290)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1938 (Box 291)
      - Rockwood, Charles P.--The Yellow River Project, 1949 (Box 291)
      - Royal Institute of International Affairs, 1933-1934, 1936-1938, 1945-1946 (Box 291)
      - Saito, Soichi--The Family System in Japan, 1933 (Box 291)
      - Soliva, Robert, 1944-1945 (Box 291)
      - Spencer, Joseph E.--Oriental Asia: A Cultural Geography, 1948-1949 (Box 291)
      - Stanford University Press, 1936 (Box 291)
      - Stein, Gunther--American Economic Policy Toward East Asia, 1946-1948 (Box 291)
      - Tamagna, Frank
        - China's Financial Position in the Aftermath of the War, 1945-1946 (Box 291)
        - Japan's International Financial Position in the Aftermath of the War (Box 291)
      - USSR Council, 1935, 1945-1946 (Box 291)
      - University of Chicago Press, 1936-1937 (Box 291)
      - Wood, Gordon L.--The Development and Defense of Australia, 1945 (Box 291)
    - Printed Material (Box 291)
    - Miscellaneous Files
      - American Council Conference, 1944 (Box 292)
      - American Council Institute of Pacific Relations Members and Officers, 1925-1937 (Box 292)
      - American Council Membership Forms, 1942 (Box 292)
      - American Council Membership List, 1940 (Box 292)
      - American Philosophical Society, 1944 (Box 292)
      - Bisson, T.A. (Box 292)
      - Buck, J. Lossing (Box 292)
      - Letters to Dr. Max Mason from Edward C. Carter (Box 292)
      - Letters to Miss Sydnor Walker from Edward C. Carter, 1938 November 21,: Appendix 1-6 (Box 292)
      - Letters to Dr. Joseph H. Willits from Edward C. Carter (Box 292)
      - Chapman, Abraham "Study of Philippine Nationalism" (Box 293)
      - Chinese History Project (Box 293)
      - Clubb, Edmund "The New Borderland" (Box 293)
      - Copyright Office (Box 293)
      - Fairbank, ProJohn (Box 293)
      - Far Eastern Survey Printing Cost (Box 293)
      - Far Eastern Survey Printing Order (Box 293)
      - Far Eastern Survey Releases (Box 293)
      - Farley, Mirian Labor in Postwar Japan (Box 293)
      - Letters From Miriam Farley to Various People with reply (Box 293)
      - Letters to Dr. Max Mason and Director of Davison Fund From F.V. Field (Box 293)
      - Financial Statements and Reports (Box 293)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 293)
      - Hot Spring Conference--Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 293)
      - IPR Bulletins and Newsletter (Box 293)
      - IPR Bulletins and Newsletter (Box 294)
      - Philip C. Jessup (Box 294)
      - Benjamin Lizer (Box 294)
      - Olga Lang (Box 294)
      - Owen Lattimore (Box 294)
      - Letters and Reports (Box 294)
      - Wellington Liu (re: Yao Chia-Chi), 1941 (Box 294)
      - Correspondence of the translation of Motilev (Box 294)
      - Rockefeller Appeal, 1938 November 21 (Box 294)
      - Rockefeller Foundation--Dr. Max Mason, 1932 November 11 (Box 294)
      - Dr. David Rowe Data Paper, 1945 (Box 294)
      - Marguerite Stewart (Box 294)
      - Henry A. Wallace (Box 294)
      - Washington Office Record of Monthly Income and Disbursements, 1942 July 26 (Box 294)
      - Wittfogel, K.A.
        - K.A. Wittfogel, 1942 (Box 295)
        - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 295)
        - Comments, 1939-1942 (Box 295)
        - Correspondence, 1939-1941, 1944 (Box 295)
        - Correspondence, Rockefeller Foundation and IPR Staff and Miscellaneous (Box 295)
        - Immigration, 1939-1942 Feng: Wang Yao (Box 295)
        - IPR Staff and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1939, 1941 (Box 295)
        - 2 Chinese Scholars (Box 295)
        - Oxford University Press (Box 295)
        - Publication Plans, 1939-1942 (Box 295)
        - Am. Phil Soc. Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 295)
        - Rockefeller Foundation, 1939, 1941-1942 (Box 295)
- Part III: Files of Individuals
  - Part III.1: F.V. Field
    - Alsberg, Dr. Carl L. (Box 296)
    - American Correspondence Committee (Box 296)
    - American Council Constitution (Box 296)
    - American Council Executive Committee (Box 296)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 296)
    - American Council Membership (Box 296)
    - American Russian Institute (Box 296)
    - Austern, 1938 (Box 296)
    - A--Miscellaneous (Box 296)
    - B--Miscellaneous (Box 296)
    - Barnes, Kathleen (Box 296)
    - Blumenthal, Annette (Box 296)
    - Boston Conference (Box 296)
    - Boycott (Box 296)
    - Budget 1938 (Box 296)
    - C--Miscellaneous (Box 296)
    - Canadian Institute International Affairs (Box 296)
    - Carnegie (Box 296)
    - Carter
      - 1938 January-March (Box 296)
      - 1938 April-December (Box 297)
    - Carter Inquiry (Box 297)
    - Chen, Han-seng (Box 297)
    - Cherrington (Box 297)
    - China Institute Bulletin (Box 297)
    - Chinese Communism (Box 297)
    - Conference, 1939 (Box 297)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 297)
    - D--Miscellaneous (Box 297)
    - Denver (Box 297)
    - Denver Group (Box 297)
    - E--Miscellaneous (Box 297)
    - Exposition (Box 297)
    - F--Miscellaneous (Box 297)
    - Fahs, C. Burton (Box 297)
    - Fall Conference Series (Box 297)
    - Farley (Box 298)
    - Field, Frederick V. (Box 298)
    - Finance Letters (Misc.) (Box 298)
    - Fisher (Box 298)
    - Fisher--Southern California (Box 298)
    - Fisheries Study (Box 298)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 298)
    - G--Miscellaneous (Box 298)
    - Graphic Handbook (Box 298)
    - Guam Investigation (Box 298)
    - Guam--Thompson, Laura (Box 298)
    - H--Miscellaneous (Box 298)
    - Hanwell, Norman (Box 298)
    - Holland, William L. (Box 298)
    - Hunsberger, Warren (Box 298)
    - Inquiry
      - Criticism of (Box 298)
      - Lockwood (Box 298)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 298)
      - Outlines (Box 298)
    - L--Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - Loomis (Box 299)
    - Mc--Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - M-- Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - Mass Education Movement (Box 299)
    - Mister [?] (Box 299)
    - N--Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - New York Staff (Box 299)
    - News on Education and Publication (Box 299)
    - O--Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - Oakie
      - January - June (Box 299)
      - July - December (Box 299)
    - P--Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - Pacific Northwest (Box 299)
    - Publication Fund (Box 299)
    - R-- Miscellaneous (Box 299)
    - Reports, 1927-1929 (Box 299)
    - Rockefeller Fellowships, 1940 (Box 300)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 300)
    - Rogers, Cornwell B. (Key to contemporary affairs) (Box 300)
    - Russian Unit (Box 300)
    - S--Miscellaneous (Box 300)
    - San Francisco
      - Bay Region Division (Box 300)
      - Executive Committee (Box 300)
      - Finances (Box 300)
    - Schumpeter (Box 300)
    - Shotwell (Box 300)
    - S.S.R.C. Meeting--FVF's speech (See Steiner under PAC. Northwest) (Box 300)
    - Southern California Division (Box 300)
    - Syllabus (Box 300)
    - T--Miscellaneous (Box 301)
    - Tamagna (Box 301)
    - Taylor (Box 301)
    - Time Table (Box 301)
    - U--Miscellaneous (Box 301)
    - Union (Box 301)
    - United Front (Box 301)
    - V--Miscellaneous (Box 301)
    - W--Miscellaneous (Box 301)
    - Wright, Louise (Box 301)
    - XYZ—Miscellaneous (Box 301)
  - Part III.2: K. Greene
    - A--Miscellaneous (Box 302)
    - American Council Executive Committee (Box 302)
    - Annual Report, 1941 (Box 302)
    - Appendices 1-6 (Box 302)
    - Applications (Box 302)
    - B--Miscellaneous (Box 302)
    - Baker, Dorothy Mrs. (Box 302)
    - Barnes, Russell (Box 302)
    - Barnett, Robert W. (Box 302)
    - Barton, R.F. (Box 302)
    - Boston Conference - N.H.T.A., 1941 November 7-8 (Box 302)
    - C--Miscellaneous (Box 302)
    - Carnegie (Box 302)
    - Carter, Edward C. (Box 302)
    - Carter, Margaret Taylor (Box 302)
    - Cleveland Conference (Box 302)
    - Committee on Pacific Relations (Box 302)
    - D--Miscellaneous (Box 303)
    - E--Miscellaneous (Box 303)
    - Ehlers (Box 303)
    - Executive and Finance Committee, 1941 March 11 (Box 303)
    - F--Miscellaneous (Box 303)
    - Far Eastern Leaflet (Box 303)
    - Far Eastern Survey Comments (Box 303)
    - Finance Appeals, 1941 Fall (Box 303)
    - Foreign Policy Assoc. - IPR Students Conference International House, 1941 December 5 (Box 303)
    - Form Finance Appeals, 1941 Spring, Summer (Box 303)
    - G--Miscellaneous (Box 303)
    - Government Contracts (Box 303)
    - Greene, Katherine R.C. (Box 303)
    - H--Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - Herod (Box 304)
    - Herod, W.R. Corporate Membership Committee (Box 304)
    - Holland (Box 304)
    - I--Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - Inparel (Box 304)
    - Inquiries
      - Literature (Box 304)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 304)
      - Study Groups (Box 304)
    - J--Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - K--Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - L--Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - Lockwood, W.W. (Box 304)
    - M---Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - Mc--Miscellaneous (Box 304)
    - Membership Regrets etc. (Box 304)
    - N--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - New Members (Box 305)
    - O--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - Pacific Council, 1941 (Box 305)
    - Personnel (Box 305)
    - S--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - Syracuse Conference, 1941 November 7-8 (Box 305)
    - T--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - Time, Life, Fortune, Inc. (Box 305)
    - Transportation (Part II) (Box 305)
    - Travellers (Box 305)
    - U--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - Union (Box 305)
    - V--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - W--Miscellaneous (Box 305)
    - Walsh-Buck (Box 305)
    - Wilbur (Box 305)
    - XYZ—Miscellaneous (Box 305)
  - Part III.3: W.L. Holland
    - 1947
      - A--Miscellaneous (Box 306)
      - Adler, S. (Box 306)
      - Advisory Sub-Committee (Box 306)
      - AMCO
        - American-Indian Relations (Box 306)
          (opions as to? outcome of a vist of delegate to India)
        - Honolulu (Box 306)
        - Los Angeles (Box 306)
        - New York (Box 306)
        - San Francisco (Box 306)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box 306)
      - American IPR--Kohlberg (Box 306)
      - Andrus, J. Russell (Box 306)
      - Apostol, Dr. Jose (Box 306)
      - Appadorai, Dr. A. India (Box 306)
      - Australian Institute International Affairs (Box 306)
      - B--Miscellaneous (Box 306)
      - Barnett, Doak (Box 306)
        (letters to Mr. Walter S. Rogers)
      - Barnett, Pat and Bob (Box 306)
      - Bauer, P.T. (Box 306)
      - Belshaw, Cyril (Box 306)
      - Belshaw, H. (Box 306)
      - Belshaw, Horace (Box 306)
        (Agrarian Problems in the Western Pacific)
      - Boeke, J.H. (Box 307)
      - Bogdan, Norbert Mr. (Box 307)
        (J. Henry Schroder Banking Corporation)
      - Borg, Dorothy (Box 307)
      - Braibanti, R.J.D. (Box 307)
      - Brand, W. (UN) (Box 307)
      - Buesst, T. (Box 307)
      - Butler, Sir Paul (Box 307)
      - C--Miscellaneous (Box 307)
      - Cady, John F. (Box 307)
      - Canadian Institute International Affairs (Box 307)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 307)
      - Carter, E.G. (Box 307)
      - Carter, ProG. (Box 307)
      - Chang-Chih-yi (Sinkiang) (Box 307)
      - Chu Tung-tsu (Box 307)
        (Chinese Law Trans.)
      - Chen, Han-Seng (Box 307)
      - Chen, Ta (Box 307)
        (Urbanization of Kunming)
      - Chiang Shu-chieh (Box 307)
        (Postwar Economic Problem of Manchuria)
      - China Institute of Economics--H.D. Fong (Box 307)
      - China Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 307)
      - Cohen, Maxwell United States and Trusteeship (Box 307)
      - Collier, John & Thompson, Laura Report on American Overseas Territories (Box 307)
      - Corbett, Percy R. (Box 307)
      - Coronado Conference American IPR, 1947 April 9-13 (Box 307)
      - D--Miscellaneous (Box 308)
      - Del Castillo, Jose Lopez (Box 308)
      - Duyvendak, ProJ.J.L. (Box 308)
      - E--Miscellaneous (Box 308)
      - Emerson, ProRupert (Box 308)
      - F--Miscellaneous (Box 308)
      - Finance other than Research (Box 308)
      - French IPR (Box 308)
      - Fry, Dr. Thomas P. "Law and Administration in New Guinea" (Box 308)
      - G--Miscellaneous (Box 308)
      - Gilchrist, Huntington (Box 308)
      - Gourou, Pierre (Box 308)
      - Grajdanzev, Andrew (Box 308)
      - Grajdanzev, Andrew--Japanese Agriculture (Box 308)
      - H--Miscellaneous (Box 308)
      - Hammer, Ellen (Box 308)
      - Healy, Mary F. (Box 308)